human dictionary 40 dollars
[Music]
infinite founders and calls themselves
proofs the teacher has a student
came to me
I give up I'm leaving this
group 70 why it's too complicated
we should just focus on our hearts
you don't need these homework
courses just do it simply speak
from the heart
open your heart all these talks
lectures schools and more schools
that's all learning
it's too much opened your heart to me and
they gave up they haven't
come back yet
[Music]
or said party pas
[Music] there is
because wanted you not to know
I found a word he doesn't know
it's 50 dollars answer the
students who especially the students who have
the high spiritual intelligence
quotient
I'm not talking about the
normal intelligence quotient
I'm talking about the spiritual
intelligence quotient I'm not talking
about guests who take the college test
answering all the math questions correctly
[Music]
I'm talking about when  Someone
attacks you so that you not only live but live even more,
that's like a spiritual
intelligence quotient, or as they say, the
rare and spiritual intelligence
quotient people
who will experience someone more when
they are attacked.
People are hungry to
get more information on the topic, they invite you to
say, "Give me more, it tasted better to me." Is
n't there just one
school that's in the lower level school? [
Laughter]
[Applause]
I could make a profit as this class
for 100 dollars. I'll give you
back if I haven't affected everything.
[Music]
100 dollars. Why? I want a precise,
accurate answer. I don't want an
answer that wanders around. Why does the
listener have the high spiritual
intelligence quotient people?
Why are they hungry for more
information on the topic? Majority?
Why do they want to know the highest school?
Why do they want to know the whole school?
[Music]
Matschie, how will it happen in a political
group? The 100 dollars
go in circles, it doesn't stop.
I want a precise, correct answer
because they  worrying and
loving everyone and wanting to help everyone, wanting to
have all the possible strategies and being able to help everyone, I've moved
[Applause]
This answer is so perfect, I give you,
gives them back then, excellent in the
restaurant, when the waiter
gives a particularly good service, there is a
tip, right, so fantastic,
with such fantastic service,
I gave a $100 tip
[Music] was, is,
although, I would like a bigger
toolbox when the plumber
comes to your house, mine is, he is
the best
[Music]
an old hippie, I don't know why
I like him, he has this long hair and
the air conditioning, I don't know why,
but I feel connected to him
somehow
[Music]
he has been doing plumbing work for 50
years, he does that, his father was a
plumber, and when you talk to him, he
is one of the few people
I can really talk to who do
n't know who I am, the
kids sit and plumbing
work, we talk about one thing, talk about
why he is, collecting tools, it's been
50 years, very performance, I have, like
a whole supermarket in a truck
Thousands of little boxes with
strange tools. Whatever breaks in
my house,
he can fix it without having to
go to a shop
because he has all the combinations of strange parts there are
in his truck. And I'm
not kidding,
ten years ago they put a
special filter in my house
for the cooling water. When
Jackson starts to complain, I call him, open the
door, and he says, "Yes, I have that."
And he has all sorts of different filters in his truck.
It's really good to know him.
[Music]
Also, something cool about this, which
is really rare,
he knows how to fix things and he shows
me how I can
fix it myself next time. He gives all the secrets.
Latour's work is free. Their
answer has to do with my plumber,
the real police. They want to know
110, 100, or hundreds of thousands. We
want to recognize 1000 because maybe
a Schiller doesn't understand the pen,
but they understand the story with
the two levels.
[Music]
Maybe there are people who do
n't know the level, but the magician,
maybe mine.  Students don't understand the
two levels, but the story
with the distinctive cocaine, by
simply being here during the last
few days, you already have a pretty
good truck in this school.
In short, body school, we are gathering new
evidence to be empty.
[Music]
Therefore, I'm sorry to have to tell you that
five white teachers would have in
half an hour,
we only have time to talk to them in
detail
about the stories, and that's a
house number 8 details with one because it's
certainly still half an hour there. Not
the first one calls things being empty.
I'll say it differently: everything in the universe is
empty because everything in the universe
is either one thing or more than one thing.
I'll say it again: everything in the universe
is either one thing or more than one
thing. For example, his nose is one thing
and your ears are two
things. His nose is one thing and your
ears are more than one thing. If you
examine everything in the universe,
either they are one thing, you can.
If you teach your students, you can.
It even makes everything in the
universe either one thing or two
things. Everything is either one thing or
more than one thing.
We don't have 21 of those before the
lesson, Peter. You were disappointed.
I won't give many details.
The second type, the second proof for the
teachers.
Speaking of which, our school of the
middle way has very, very many
proofs for the teaching time. So, the
second proof for the teaching time is called
the diamond chip proof. So, if
you break a diamond, then there
are many individual chips.
So, the second proof
in this class is called the proof of the
diamond chip. That in Tibetan German
[music]
German-German is called diamond.
That doesn't mean the king of stones, the king of stones.
And bam, it means if
you break a glass,
when do you get all these small pieces?
Then you say to a person, be
careful, those are probably
glass shards, the small, pointed,
sharp-edged pieces. The second proof of
the teaching time that
we are talking about is the proof of the
diamond chip. The third course is coming;
it is difficult in the  During the pause, a
young woman was with me.
[Music]
Clever mum or dad
taught me how to plant seeds and at the
same time how to plant spiritual seeds.
Whatever, she was very proud. She
came to me. It was a small flowerpot,
and from there the sprout came straight out.
Bachelor, I planted that.
That's also a quality a
teacher must have: accept every
gift with grace.
In your mind, do you think, "
Should I put this in my
suitcase?"
Every whole suitcase. Patrick,
thank you.
And then he said it wasn't a
gift. I only wanted to
show it,
and suddenly I wanted to keep it. I don't know
why, but suddenly I wanted to keep it. Give it
back.
[Music] Wo
n't you give it to me? We said yes. No,
why are we talking about this before the
sprout showed itself?
What was in the pot? Say yes or no. Yes. Guest
camp was looking.
And then she watered it, and the
cream is also his. It opened,
and the sprout came out. In the
Catholic Church, it's called Essex
Nilo. It comes from nothing, from nothing, from
nothing.
And you can have this discussion about the
creation of the world. At the Big Bang,
everything came from nothing. Was there
something in the pot, or was there nothing in the
pot that produced this sprout, or from
which this castle emerged? Did
the sprout grow from nothing,
or did the sprout grow out of something?
I read your thoughts. You're thinking, "Of
course it came from the seed."
[Music]
It's that something that was there that grew.
If you have the pot without a seed, then
nothing will grow.
Obviously, if you give me a choice,
which view is correct?
[Music] Does the
little girl's sprout come
from a seed, or did it
arise from nothing? I know what
he's thinking.
The sprout came from the seed.
And when I become a mother, and I will, when
I become a mother, I would
say both are wrong.
The sprout didn't arise from nothing,
and it didn't
grow from something.
That's the third proof. Sorry,
the third proof.
That's the  The idea wouldn't have elaborated on
emerging things from something
else
[Music]
like when the teacher explained to me that my
mind is like a long spaghetti noodle
or was there nothing nothing nothing big
bang big bang me it's right and
butter says neither of them
commitments says neither of them it
's so frustrating
I'm glad I'm not married to him
and that I don't have to go to
work
Kengo the fourth proof of majority that
we study in Year 8
[Music]
Year 8 the fourth proof for the doctrine ready ready
the sprout the little girl
has shown herself there are
other
choices we can talk about there is another
group of four
number one
[Music]
the sprout has emerged from itself
the sprout comes from the sprout that's
actually impossible but we have to
consider every possibility is a
sprout from itself choice
number one or number two priest
from something else for example
from a seed don't choose yet listen to
the other two or
or comes the  sprout from something that is a
combination of nothing and something else,
that's the third time, the fourth
choice,
or does it come from nothing?
I'll say it again, four options. If it's a
lesson, you can do it like this:
40 dollars,
I'll give you four options.
Where does the sprout number one come from? From
itself. The
sprout weapon was already there a year ago,
and today it has shown itself.
[Music]
And by the way, there are schools in
Hinduism that believe that the
main school believes that the
second option is that
the sprout is something that came from something like a seed.
The third option is that
the sprout arose from nothing and
from itself and from something
else. And the fourth choice is that it
is the sprout that arose from
nothing. Which of the four
options do you want? In English, let's say
none of the four.
That's the fourth proof.
[Music]
So we're going to do another proof now. But that
also means that we haven't
finished, that we haven't finished
our work, and that we have to meet again.
Yes, applause for
the translator, all those who are actually for
the  Departure planned at 12,
the bus leaves at 12:30. If
the bus leaves at 12:30, for those who
were planned on the 12 bus, the
12 bus leaves at 12:30.
Then I can give the fifth proof.
Okay, I have
[Music]
the fifth proof for the apprenticeship, which is called
dependent emergence, sometimes it is
the last one, it is called the bike path gap.
Nick Becker, the king of
logic, the best proof for the apprenticeship, that's why
he is called the king of proofs
for the majority.
[Music]
I have seven more minutes, do
you want to know more about it?
I like you, you are good listeners.
This last proof, which is the king of all
proofs, is empty because it is
dependent emergence, and it can be
interpreted in three ways. And it
's totally cool if you have these in your
budissa, two trucks. If you
were a teacher yourself, someone wants to get a
divorce.
[Music]
But then you can say, no, no, don't get
divorced, I still have something.
I still have something in  I
can get that repaired, I'll have it fixed next
week. China tried it, but my three
solutions are worth trying to find out if
it works. Speaking of which, if you have a
teacher
[Music],
that's one of the most common questions
we get asked.
I lived with my boyfriend like that, and
yesterday I thought about breaking up with
him. And one of the
best things you
can answer is: visit the same age group again
in two weeks. The city finds out, and then
after the three [times] already prove
the dependency arising, maybe that will
help. Maybe you wo
n't have to get a divorce then. And then they wait
two weeks, and then it doesn't matter
if that's explained right or wrong
because if they wait two weeks,
then the anger will have already dissipated. If
they wait two weeks and
eat waffles for two weeks, then they won't get a divorce.
They won't get a divorce.
Postponing solves the problem very often
because they remember that they
actually love each other.
I have to think a little now
[Music],
here's the advice for the woman who
argues with her husband in the kitchen
after lower school.
The advice  The lowest
interpretation of dependent origination,
I know it almost always applies to me. Someone should do it.
What's your problem? He said I
'm stupid. Yeah, he writes like in the kitchen all the time.
Look here, you can apply the teacher.
[Music]
That's instructive. The majority means there's
a reason why he's upset.
[Music]
It's in the kitchen. There's no husband who gets upset for
no reason. The lowest
interpretation of dependent origination: maybe he
was hungry, maybe
he was tired,
maybe he had a
fight at work.
Everything has a reason.
[Music]
A husband who gets upset for no reason... It's
empty. There's no such husband. That
's the lowest explanation. It
's still dependent origination.
Now we go a few steps
upwards.
You don't have to get upset.
He has many parts. You're focusing
on the negative parts.
He has a loving part. He's good with
children.
He gives... After dinner, he
really hugs you.
He also has good parts. He's not just
one part.
There are many aspects to your husband.
One part is a...  The problem is, he gets
angry really quickly, but he focuses
on the good parts. He's done well with the
children, he earns money,
and later in the evening, you know,
he has many good parts.
That's the second stage of dependent
emergence. Things are dependent on
his part. The first stage: things are
dependent on causes. He's simply
hungry, tired.
He had problems at work. That's the
lowest level of
dependent emergence. A little
further up, on the second stage, he
also has good sides.
Nobody is just one thing.
He also has many good qualities. He's good
with the children,
he earns the money for the family. He's
temperamental, but he also has other
parts. That's the middle stage of
dependent emergence.
And now we go to the highest stage,
and then we have completed the retreat. And
it is truly auspicious
that he ends with the
highest stage and highest explanation.
And I
still owe you others how much I owe you,
but this is the king. Now it begins.
You know, Valais railway. Well,
then we have everything we
need. Your husband, you  You have problems
with my husband? Yes,
may I ask you a question? He's
writing to me. Yes, yes, yes, I'd like to ask a
question. Do
you ever write to your children?
Maybe if you yell at your children,
maybe you'll plant a tame one
in your mind, and then next
week when you come into the kitchen, the
seed will open, and maybe, maybe,
everyone in the world will get what they
deserve.
[Music]
Soon there will be 100%
justice in the universe.
[Music]
Maybe they are. Is it so that
they also write to Switzerland?